Guide to the Visual AIDS Records MSS.503
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III. Day With(out) Art, 1989-2013; 15 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, 8 flat-file folders, and 9 items in 3 shared boxes; 2 audiocassettes; 2 VHS
  - Bravo Television "Moment Without Television Unfinished Stories" -- Press Kit, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - World AIDS Day Coalition -- Meeting Material, Drafts, Member Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Logos, Graphic Art Design -- Proofs, 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Proclamation Certificates from Manhattan -- "Day Without Art and Night Without Light" Day, 1990-1995 (Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 12)
  - Information Sheets, Press Releases, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Participant Response Forms and Lists, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2-6)
  - Participant Event Material, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 7, Box 36, Folder 1-4, Box 66, Folder 7-8)
  - Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5, Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Bravo Television "Moment Without Television Unfinished Stories" -- Press Releases, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Every Ten Minutes Project -- Project Description, Partner List, Press Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Every Ten Minutes Project -- Recording Created by Robert Farber for Visual AIDS and Day Without Art, 1992
    - Audio Recording (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 503_0002)
    - Audio Recording (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 503_0003)
  - Night Without Light -- Promotional Material, Information Sheet, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - World AIDS Day Coalition -- Correspondence, Information Sheets, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - The AIDS Bottle Project Sponsored by the Institute of Cultural Inquiry -- Information Sheet, Press Release, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Posters, 1991-1992 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - World AIDS Day Coalition Meeting Notice, January 23, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Phone List, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Fliers, Notes, Media Releases, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - "Face It, Lick It" Poster-Related, Poster Negative, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12, Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaire and Survey, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Agreement with Creative Time Regarding Artists, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Poster-Related -- Master Mailing List, Photographs of Poster Rolling Event, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Participant Lists, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Participant Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2-6, Box 67, Folder 2, Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 8)
  - Participant Event Posters, 1992 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - PositiveGram Postcards, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Boston Institute of Contemporary Art -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 78, Vhs 503_0018)
  - Canada -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Chicago -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Indiana -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Seattle -- Participant Event Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 7-9, Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Night Without Light -- Promotional Material, Information Sheet, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Proclamation Certificate -- Borough of Manhattan Proclaims "Day Without Art and Night Without Light" Day, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Bravo Television Promotional Material, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - "We Interrupt This Program" Project -- Report, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - New York State Council -- Final Report, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Participant Event Material, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Letterhead, Forms, Logos, Posters, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 1, Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Informational Fliers, Participant Form, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 1992 Poster Copyright Issues -- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - T-shirt Sale Order Forms, Sale Lists, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - "Tired of Hearing About HIV?..." Poster -- Graphics, Proofs, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - The AIDS Bottle Project Sponsored by the Institute of Cultural Inquiry -- Information Packet, Letter, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - "We Interrupt This Program" Project -- Agreement with Creative Time, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Steering Committee Notes, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Poster Rolling Event -- Instructions, Notes, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Project Notes, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - AIDS Theatre Project -- Completed Visual AIDS Survey Form, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Completed Participant Forms, Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1993 (Box 40, Folder 15, Box 41, Folder 1-4, Box 67, Folder 5, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 13, Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 7)
  - Participant Event Material, circa 1993-1999 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Canada -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Chicago -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - New England -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - New York State -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Washington, DC -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - West Coast -- Participant Event Material, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Press Clippings, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1-2, Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Night Without Light -- Correspondence, Press Clippings, Contact Lists, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs -- Funding Agreement, Financial Report, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Day Without Art: 5 College Student Videos about AIDS, circa 1993 (Box 78, Vhs 503_0019)
  - Promotional Posters, 1993-1996 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Participant Survey Responses, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Letterhead, Logo Graphics, circa 1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Fliers, Brochures, Forms, Press Releases, Fact Sheets, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Poster Rolling Event -- Volunteer List, Notes, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Funder List, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Completed Participant Forms, Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12-13, Box 43, Folder 1, Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Kingwood College -- Participant Event Photographs, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - New York -- Participant Event Material, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Wichita -- Participant Event Material, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "In the Picture: The Art World Cares" Event -- Press Release, Agenda, Invitation Letters, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Night Without Light -- Promotional Fliers, Information Packets, Correspondence, Participant Confirmation Forms, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Brochures, Fact Sheets, Press Releases, Letterhead, Logo Graphics, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Posters -- Original Images, Proofs, and Graphics, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 10, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Participant Event Material, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 1-3, Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Houston -- Participant Event Information Kit, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia -- Participant Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Night Without Light -- Information Kit, Completed Participant Forms, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - World AIDS Day Resource Package, 1995-1998 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Brochure, Event Listings, Press Releases / Media Alerts, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Poster Idea Graphics, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - PSA Material -- Print Advertisements, Letters to Potential Sponsors, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 11, Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Web Action Project -- Description, Promotional Material, Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - "Bardo" Project -- Proposal from The Contemporary Art Institute of New York, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Participant Event Material, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1, Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Congress Speeches Referencing HIV, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Night Without Light -- Completed Participant Forms, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Brochure, Print Advertisements, Promotional Sticker, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 6, Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Poster -- "AIDS Zone", 1997 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Completed Participant Forms and Event Material, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
  - Houston -- Participant Event Information Kit, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Web Action Event -- Press Releases, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Press Clippings, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Time Capsule for Day Without Art Website with ArtAIDS, Creative Time, and MoMA -- Proposal, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Material, Information Kit, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Poster Creation -- Notes, Correspondence, Printing Proofs, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 16, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 15)
  - Poster Negative Sheets -- "AIDS is Over, Right?" and Other Advertisement, 1998, undated (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Participant Event Material, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Houston -- Participant Event Information Kit, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Press Clippings, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Projects in Development -- Descriptions, Letters, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - "A Day in the Life" Project -- Forms, Copies of Journal Entries, Sketches, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - "Absent Image" Project -- Description, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - The AIDS Bottle Project Sponsored by the Institute of Cultural Inquiry -- Information Packet, Letter, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit -- Ricardo Morin and Niccolo Cataldi at St. Mark's -- Promotional Material, List of Artworks, Correspondence, November - December 1998 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Night Without Light -- Participant Lists, Letters, Press Releases, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, Notes, Press Contact Lists, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 8-10)
  - Print Advertisements and Related, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Website -- Copies of Related Content, Web Action Listings, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 12-13)
  - Participant Response Forms, Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1999 (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
  - MoMA -- Event Material, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Night Without Light -- Participant Response Forms, Letters, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Participant Event Material, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Cultural Capital/Cultural Labor Conference Panel Discussion -- Correspondence, AIDS Fact Sheet, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Night Without Light -- Correspondence, Participant Response Forms, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Participant Event Material, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 9, Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Award Presentation Agenda and List of Artists Lost to AIDS, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - House of Frame by Frame Fierce Project -- Forms, Letters, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Night Without Light -- Participant Forms, Press Clipping, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Participant Event Material, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Press Clipping, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Print Advertisements, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Participant Event Material, 2004, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Print Advertisements, 2005, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Press Clippings, 2006-2010 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Participant Event Material, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Screening of Untitled -- Information Kit, Event Press Release, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Exhibit Photographs at Unknown Location, 2011-2012 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - The Painting Center / Visual AIDS Exhibit Grant Proposal, circa 2011 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Participant Event Material, 2012-2013 (Box 47, Folder 23, Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Participant Event Poster, undated (Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 21)
  - Night Without Light -- Buttons, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Information Sheets, Fee Agreement Form, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Unknown Event Photographs, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Promotional Poster, undated (Flat-file-folder 4 left)
  - Black Cloth Banner with White Print -- "Art is Not Enough", undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Series IV. Electric Blanket, 1990-1995; 5 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 7 items in 2 shared boxes; 8 audiocassettes
  This series documents Electric Blanket, a slide show art installation created by Visual AIDS to address the AIDS crisis. The installation was first projected on December 1, 1990, on the facade of Cooper Union in New York City for Day Without Art. Materials in this series include event planning files, press releases, promotional materials, press clippings, correspondence, fact sheets, and information kits. Slides and audio recordings used in the presentation are also in this series. Additionally, files related to the traveling installation include lists of venues and schedules, notes, as well as individual city files containing installation instructions, notes, promotional materials, and photographs from each event.
  - Press Releases, Forms, Photographs, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Fact Sheet, Information Packs, Promotional Material, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Planning Notes, circa 1990 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Photographs -- Images Used in Installation, circa 1990s (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Photographs -- Crowds Viewing the First Installation in New York and Subsequent Venues, 1990, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Release Forms, Related Photographs, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Slides Used in Installation, circa 1990s (Box 48, Folder 3-12, Box 49, Folder 1-6)
  - Notes for Slides, circa 1990s (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Slides -- Steve Hart Images, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Promotional / Information Kits, circa 1990s (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Speaking Engagements at Rutgers University -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, 1991, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Planning Notes, Descriptions, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Photographs -- Installation Shown in Michigan, January 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Project Description, Promotional Material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Funding for Electric Blanket Tour -- Application, Final Report, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - List of Installation Tour Stops, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Various Venues Promotional, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Allen Frame -- Budgets, Letters, 1992-1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Budapest Installation -- Allen Frame and Frank Franca Correspondence and Notes, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - List of Artist Photographers in Show, 1993, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Press / Information Kit, circa 1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Project Description, Release Forms, and Photographs of Images Used in Installation and of Audience, circa 1993 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Press Clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Promotional Material, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Lists of Artworks and Artists, January 1994 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Visual Artists Public Projects -- Letter and Slides, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Project Description, Press Clippings, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - List of Installation Venues / Locations (1990-1994) (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Installation Locations -- Atlanta -- Press Release, Press Clippings, Photograph, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 18-19)
  - Installation Locations -- Australia -- Letters, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Installation Locations -- Baltimore -- Financial Reports, Exhibition Documentation, November 15, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Installation Locations -- Birmingham -- Letter, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Installation Locations -- Brooklyn -- Promotional Material, Correspondence, Press Releases, Press Clippings, July 23, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Installation Locations -- Budapest -- Press Clipping, Note, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Installation Locations -- Colorado -- Slide Show Story Board, Notes, circa 1992 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Installation Locations -- Drexel University -- Event Announcement, March 5, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Installation Locations -- Finland -- Letter, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Installation Locations -- Gay Games -- Agreement, Letter, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Installation Locations -- Germany -- Correspondence, Press Clipping, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Installation Locations -- Glasgow, Scotland -- Project Description, Correspondence, Promotional Material, October - December 1992 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Installation Locations -- Heartlove Productions -- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Installation Locations -- Illinois State University -- Letter, Promotional Material, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Installation Locations -- Jackson, Mississippi -- Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Installation Locations -- Japan -- Correspondence, Press Clippings, Project Description, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Installation Locations -- London -- Promotional Material, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Installation Locations -- Mary Washington College -- Promotional Material, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Installation Locations -- Memphis -- Press Release, circa 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Installation Locations -- Miami -- Promotional Material, Press Releases, Press Clippings, March 24, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Installation Locations -- Oslo -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Installation Locations -- Philadelphia Museum of Art -- Promotional Material, September 18, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Installation Locations -- Rhode Island College -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Installation Locations -- Seattle -- Installation Storyboard, Correspondence, Promotional Material, Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
  - Installation Locations -- Toronto -- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Installation Locations -- Washington, DC -- Promotional Material, April 24, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Fact Sheet, 1990s (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Installation Audio Tracks, 1990s
    - Side A, Side B (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0004)
    - Side C, Side D (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0005)
    - Side E, Side F (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0009)
    - Side G, Side H (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0010)
  - Installation Audio Track, 1990s (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 503_0001)
  - Installation Audio Track, 1990s (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0007)
  - Installation Audio Track, 1990s (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0008)
  - Installation Audio Track, 1990s (Box Shared Fales 123, Audiocassette 503_0011)
- Series V. The Archive Project, 1986-2013; 6.50 Linear Feet in 11 manuscript boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  Visual AIDS began The Archive Project in 1994 in an effort to collect, describe, preserve, and provide access to the personal papers, audiovisual materials, publications, and ephemera created, dealing with, or collected by HIV-positive artists. Material in this series documents the formation and marketing of the Archive Project as well as planning files for exhibitions inspired by material from artists' files. This series also contains a small collection of individual artists' files containing resumes, exhibition material, and artwork images.
  Arrangement
  Organized into 3 subseries:
  Subseries V.A. Project Documentation
  Subseries V.B. Exhibits
  Subseries V.C. Artists' Files
  Material within these subseries are in chronological, with the exception of the last, which is in alphabetical order.
  - Subseries V.A. Project Documentation, 1989-2013; 2.50 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 1 oversize flat box
    This subseries contains material related to the formation, administration, and marketing of the Archive Project including correspondence, promotional material, artwork image use documentation, and committee meeting minutes and notes. This subseries also contains material related to the partnership between The Estate Project and Visual AIDS which was connected to the formation of the Archive Project. Files related to use of artwork images by outside organizations are also in this subseries.
    - Correspondence, 1989-2003 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Information Sheet, Press Release, List, 1989-1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Artists' Caucus -- Meeting Minutes, Promotional Material, Documentation on Project Formation, 1990-1998 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - The Archive Project Zine Drawings, circa 1990s (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Estate Project Partnership / Collaboration -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, Notes, 1991-1999 (Box 51, Folder 16-17)
    - Estate Project Partnership / Collaboration -- Artist Release Forms, Contracts and Letters Related to the Virtual Collection, 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - Archive Slide File Forms, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Proposal, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - NPR Show Interview -- Script, Press Clipping, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Archive Committee -- Agenda, Notes, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Archive Committee -- Agenda, Notes, Minutes, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Carrie Yamaoka -- Project Letterhead and Logo Design, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Print Advertisements, 1995, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 12, Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Archive Project Artists' Images Used in Outside Publications, 1995-2009 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Completed Artists' Release Forms, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Nick Debs Correspondence, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Art Supply Service Program -- Requests, Letters, 1996, undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Frank Moore Party -- Correspondence, Descriptions, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Tom McGovern Book Publishing Project -- Proposal, Letter, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Ann Meredith Project on Lesbians with AIDS (Not Completed) -- Negatives of Images, Letters, Project Description, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Speech Script from HIV Arts Network Event, May 22, circa 1997 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - List of MoMA Artworks by Artists with HIV / AIDS, circa 1997 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - In the Life Media -- Film Project Using Artwork Images from Archive -- Release Forms, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Promotional Cards for the Artists' Registry, circa 2013 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Subseries V.B. Exhibits, 1995-2005; 2.70 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes